wetnwildbeauty.com 2018-10-11

# Privacy Policy

#### MARKWINS' PRIVACY POLICY

Markwins Beauty Products, Inc. (“Markwins”) has adopted a set of privacy principles applicable to our website, domain name and any other linked pages, features, content, or application services (including without limitation any mobile application services) offered from time to time by Markwins in connection therewith (collectively, the “Website” or “website”), including for example: wetnwildbeauty.com. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use and share information we obtain both online and off-line.

Markwins is committed to protecting your private information while you surf the Website. We want to keep all the visitors to the Website happy and secure, so we urge you to read the entire Policy (and if you are under 13 your parents must read it with you) so that you will know what Markwins does with the private information you provide to us. From time to time Markwins may revise our information collection and use practices or the features of our Website or technology. Any changes will be posted in the Policy and the effective date will be updated. You should review the Policy periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices. If Markwins materially changes its practices regarding information collection or use, your information will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of and have not objected to the change. Your continued use of the Website after notification indicates that you do not object to any changes in the Policy.

#### GENERAL PRIVACY POLICY TERMS  
COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

When you use the Website, you may voluntarily submit personally identifiable information (“PII”) that can be used to contact or identify you and administer your account. PII may include, but is not limited to, your name, telephone number, credit card information, mailing address and e-mail address.

Sometimes we collect PII from consumers in manual format or off-line, such as a post card or subscription form. Providing detailed notice in those situations often proves impractical, so consumers will instead be provided with a short notice that describes how to obtain the full text of the Policy and other relevant information.

We may also obtain PII from reputable third parties. When we connect information that we obtain from third parties with PII that we have collected from the Website, we will treat the acquired information like the information that we collected ourselves, and, except as permitted by the Policy, will not disclose the information to third parties.

#### COLLECTION BY AUTOMATED SYSTEMS

We may collect and log certain non-personally identifying information which a user’s browser makes available whenever a user visits the Website (“Log Data”). This information may include a user’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address (a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet), home server domain name, computer type, browser type, browser language, as well as the date and time of a user’s visit. We use Log Data to administer, operate, develop, and improve the Website by tracking and storing information in the aggregate as it relates to user’s movement within the Website such as the pages from which the user was referred, entry and exit points for the Website, search terms, pages a user visits, page views/impressions, access times, domain names and browser types. None of the Log data is linked to a user’s PII.

Like many websites, we also use “cookies” to collect information. Cookies are small bits of information that the Website places on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies remember information about your activities on the Website and enable Markwins to make your visits to the Website more enjoyable. For example, cookies can store your password for easy logon to a site you have previously visited or can save your preferences for a personalized home page.

Markwins may use cookies and similar tools to relate your use of the Website to PII obtained from you or a reputable third party. For example, if you've asked us to send you information about our upcoming products or promotions, cookie and/or click stream data about your activities on the Website may allow us to limit the materials we send you to items we think you will find interesting, based on your prior online activities and preferences. However, if Markwins wishes to combine your PII and cookie or click stream information in this manner, we will obtain your express affirmative consent. Third party advertisements displayed on the Website may also contain cookies set by internet advertising companies or advertisers. Markwins does not control these cookies and visitors to the Website sent by internet advertisers or other companies, should check the privacy policy of the advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies.

You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the Website you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Website or all functionality of the services.

We may also use web beacons on the Website. A web beacon, also known as a “web bug,” is a small, graphic image on a Web page, in a Web-based document or in an e-mail message that is designed to allow us to monitor visitors to the Website, the IP address of the computer to which the Web beacon is sent, the URL of the page from which the Web beacon comes, and the time it was viewed. None of this information is linked to a user’s PII.

#### DO NOT TRACK SETTINGS

Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your browser to let the sites you visit know that you don't want them collecting certain info about you. At this time, the Websites do not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, which may include ‘do not track’ instructions. For more information, including how to turn on Do Not Track, visit donottrack.us Third parties that have content embedded on the Websites may set cookies on a user’s browser and/or obtain information about the fact that a web browser visited the Websites from a certain IP address. Third parties cannot collect any other personally identifiable information the Websites unless you provide it to them directly.

USE OF PII

Markwins may use your PII in the following ways:

Website Updates or Promotion Information: Users of the Website may request to receive regular updates or promotional information from the Website by providing an email address. If the requester indicates that he or she is under the age of 13 the CHILDREN’S PRIVACY POLICY governs the request. Each update includes a way to unsubscribe from receiving further updates and a link to the Policy. Markwins will not combine contact information collected exclusively to fulfill a user’s request for updates with any other information collected on the Website.

E-Commerce: Our Website may offer users the chance to purchase products. Users will need to provide PII in order to complete purchase transactions. If you are not comfortable with our policies, do not make a purchase through our Website.

#### DISCLOSURE OF PII

Markwins may share your PII with our service providers, affiliates, and vendors. Provided you have given us consent, Markwins may also share your PII with advertisers and business partners that are not affiliated with Markwins but would like to send you information about their products and services. Markwins’ employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your PII. Markwins may share your PII with outside contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities (i.e., sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses) but they may only use your PII to provide Markwins with a specific service and not for any other purpose.

There may be instances when Markwins may disclose PII without providing you with notice or choice in order to protect the legal rights of Markwins or other companies affiliated with Markwins or their employees, agents and contractors; to protect the safety and security of visitors to the Website; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if Markwins sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, Markwins may transfer your PII to a third party as part of that transaction.

Except as otherwise provided in the Policy, Markwins will only use a consumer's Personally Identifiable Information for internal purposes and will not share it with any third party unless Markwins has the good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to:

  * cooperate with law enforcement authorities or comply with legal process;
  * protect the property and rights of Markwins, its affiliates or a third party;
  * protect the safety of the public or any person;
  * prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable;
  * complete, as permitted by law, a business sale, asset transfer, merger, acquisition or reorganization; or
  * fix or debug problems with the Website’ servers, software or service.

We may employ third party service providers to provide services on our behalf or to perform services related to administration of the Website (including, without limitation, maintenance, hosting and database management services, web analytics, payment processing and administration). These third parties have access to Personally Identifiable Information only to the extent necessary to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use Personally Identifiable Information for any other purpose.

We may share anonymous, aggregated information with third parties, provided that it is not traceable to any particular user. We will only do so under a contract which requires the third party assisting us to keep such information anonymous.

#### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

Markwins’ Website may be linked to internet sites operated by other companies. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with Markwins logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by Markwins. Markwins’ Website may also carry advertisements from other companies. Markwins is not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to the Website or for the privacy practices of third party or national internet advertising companies. Once you've left the Website via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any PII they collect from you.

The Website may also be linked to sites operated by companies affiliated with Markwins. Although affiliated entities adhere to the Policy, visitors to those affiliated sites should still refer to their separate privacy policies and practices, which may differ in some respects from this Policy.

#### INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER

Your PII may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to Markwins, please be advised that we transfer PII to the United States and process it there. Your consent to the Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

#### MARKWINS PROTECTS THE SECURITY OF PII

Markwins uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PII in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, Markwins uses reasonable methods to make sure that PII is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete.

#### HOW TO ACCESS, CORRECT OR DELETE YOUR PII

Visitors to the Website may review the PII we maintain about them. If you would like to review, correct, or delete this information, please contact Markwins through any of the following options:

Via post or email: Attn: Wet n Wild Brand Manager (On-line Privacy), Markwins Beauty Products, Inc., 22067 Ferrero Parkway, City of Industry, CA 91789, or by e-mail at: [customercare@WetnWildBeauty.com](mailto:customercare@WetnWildBeauty.com)

#### REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE: HOW TO CONTACT MARKWINS ABOUT PRIVACY CONCERNS

Markwins welcomes any suggestions on how to make Markwins a better and safer place. If you would like to communicate with us about the Policy or if you have privacy issues or complaints regarding the Policy, please contact us through any of the following options:

Attn: Wet n Wild Brand Manager (On-line Privacy), Markwins Beauty Products, Inc., 22067 Ferrero Parkway, City of Industry, CA 91789, or by e-mail at: [customercare@WetnWildBeauty.com](mailto:customercare@WetnWildBeauty.com)

#### ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY POLICY

The Policy outlines the information usage practices of Markwins. By accessing, browsing or using this Website or by submitting PII to Markwins you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of the Policy.

#### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

A business subject to California Civil Code section 1798.83 is required to disclose to its California customers, upon request, the identity of any third parties to whom the business has disclosed Personally Identifiable information within the previous calendar year, along with the type of Personally Identifiable Information disclosed, for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please contact us through any of the following options:

Attn: Wet n Wild Brand Manager (On-line Privacy), Markwins Beauty Products, Inc., 22067 Ferrero Parkway, City of Industry, CA 91789, or by e-mail at: [customercare@WetnWildBeauty.com](mailto:customercare@WetnWildBeauty.com)

#### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY POLICY

Markwins is especially sensitive to the need to protect the interests of children and does not intend to collect personal information from children under the age of 13, except on websites depcifically directed to Children. On those websites Markwins will follow the additional, special policies applies to applies to the collection, use or disclosure of personally identifiable information from visitors who are under the age of 13.

#### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

From time to time, we may change the Privacy Policy. We will provide notice to if these changes are material and, where required by applicable law, we will obtain consent before continued collection.

Effective Date: 09/07/15
